setmp3.com 2014-11-22

# Setkit | Privacy Policy

We have the opportunity to move not only toward the rich society and the powerful society, but upward to the Great Society.  

| 

You privacy is very important to us, accordingly, we have developed this policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose and make use of your personal information. Our privacy policies vary according to user preferences and specific tools on Setkit may have their specific policies that is valid only for that tool. For a better explanation we have split our privacy policy to the following categories:

  * General Site Policy
  * Log Files
  * Cookies & Web Beacons
  * DoubleClick DART Cookie

## General site policy

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes the consumer's domain name and e-mail address (where possible).

We collect the domain name and e-mail address (where possible) of visitors to our Web page, the e-mail addresses of those who post messages to our bulletin board, the e-mail addresses of those who make postings to our chat areas, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations, name and address.

The information we collect is used for internal review and is then discarded, used to improve the content of our Web page, used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site, used by us to contact consumers for marketing purposes, disclosed when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Website and applicable laws or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Website.

You will not receive any marketing or occasional emails unless your subscribe to our mailing list. If you supply us with your postal address on-line you will only receive the information for which you provided us your address.

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to no information that we have collected and that we maintain about other users.

Upon request we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information.

With respect to security: We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information

## Log files

Like many other Web sites, www.setkit.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

## Cookies and web beacons

www.setkit.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

## DoubleClick DART cookie

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.setkit.com 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.setkit.com and other sites on the Internet
  *  Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.setkit.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

www.setkit.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.setkit.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

| 

|  | Certain features are only available to members, to make the most of Setkit **join us** for free!  
---|---  

## Updates

| Be the **first to know** when we add new features & receive occasional set emails!  
---|---
